你们好
Hi, you guys.
怎么了
What's the matter?
又是那种很讨厌的状况
Well, it's just... lt's one of these situations that l just hate.
有一个客人给我三张票
You know, a massage client gave me three tickets...
去摩根却斯博物馆看展览
...to the Helmut Peltz Exhibit at the Morgan Chase Museum.
你觉得你得跟他上床还人情是吧
Now you're thinking you gotta sleep with him.
不是  他给我三张票
No. No. lt's just that he gave me three tickets
但是我们有六个人
and there are six of us.
-我弃权  -我也是
- l'll give up my ticket. - Me too.
你们真大方
Okay. That's so generous.
罗斯应该也很大方
And l think Ross is generous too.
太好了  那我们女生自己去
Great! OK. Then it's just us girls.
太好了
Great. Yeah.
是什么展览来着
So what is the exhibit?
主要是
lt's mostly just photographs...
女同志性爱摄影展
...of lesbian love scenes interspersed
还可以打电动  吃免费三明治
with video games and free sandwiches.
讨厌啦
Oh, man!
罗斯  听着
Hey, Ross, listen.
钱德勒害你周末
Chandler got you out
不能去女同志三明治博物馆了
of going to the lesbian sandwich museum this weekend.
谢谢  我有节目了
Thanks, but l have plans.
伊丽莎白和我要一起出游
Elizabeth and l are going out of town.
恭喜你们
That's great!
这样你就可以大赚一笔
Think about all the money that you're gonna make.
什么意思
Why? What?
她爸找你去当保姆酬劳很棒吧
Well, her father pays you for babysitting, right?
真好笑  但你们也笑太久了吧
That's funny. But maybe it's time to move on.
也是时候适可而止啦
You know, let it go. Stop it!
况且瑞秋在和伊丽莎白的爸爸交往
Besides, Rachel's going out with Elizabeth's father...
而他比她大多了
...so he's much older than she is.
看来不只是我对"化石"有兴趣
Looks like l'm not the only one interested in fossils.
罗斯  这只会提醒我们  你爱化石
Ross, all that does is remind us that you're interested in fossils.
好吧
Okay, okay.
瑞秋想和他甜言蜜语  可得用吼的
Rachel's gonna need to yell sweet nothings in his ear.
-罗斯  -拜托  这句很好笑啊
- Ross? - Come on! you guys! That's funny. Y'know?
因为他得戴助听器  因为...
Because he's gonna... He's got, like, a hearing aid.
因为他很老
Because he's all old.
失陪一下
One second.
听着  罗斯
Okay, look, Ross.
因为丽莎很喜欢你
Just so you know, since Lizzie likes you so much...
我决定接受你们交往的事
...l've accepted the fact that you're dating her.
真的  太好了
Really? OK. That's great.
是啊  但后来我又反悔了
Yeah, but then l changed my mind.
我这人就这么阴晴不定
l'm funny like that.
我已经告诉她了  现在我告诉你
So l told Lizzie, now l'm telling you.
我不希望你再和我女儿见面
l don't want you seeing my daughter anymore.
好  我知道你很不高兴
Alright. Look, l realize it upsets you.
没错
Yes, it does.
但伊丽莎白和我都是成年人
But Elizabeth and l are both adults...
所以你也拿我们没办法
...so l don't think there's anything you can do about it.
我会告诉学校你们在交往
l'll call the university and tell them about your relationship
让你被开除
and have you fired.
哎哟  有备而来喔
Oh, a man with a plan!
好兴奋喔
This is so exciting.
你的照片又要重回名人墙了
You can get your picture back up on the wall of fame.
之前被挂在墙上时  感觉好棒
It was so cool when l was up there before.
我经常和吉姆·贝路西说笑
Me and Jim Belushi would just be cracking up about something.
我被《我们的岁月》开除后  照片被拿下来
l get fired off Days of Our Lives and he takes me down.
现在他都嘲笑我
Now he's just laughing at me.
你看那个自鸣得意的混蛋
Look at him. That smug Belushi bastard!
好吧  也许你可以挂在
Okay. Maybe when they put your picture back up...
麦特·劳尔旁边
...they could put you by Matt Lauer.
你看他在对我微笑
Look at him just smiling at me.
我知道  我们会是神仙眷侣
Yeah, l know. We'd be great together.
-我回来了  -你是谁
- So l'm back. - Who are you?
乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani.
我之前上过墙
From the wall?
也许这样你会想起来
Okay, maybe this will jog your memory.
总之
Okay, anyway.
我可以回墙上了
l'm ready to go back up on the wall.
我主演了一出新戏
l'm the star of a new TV show.
-告诉我哪一出  -还没开播呢
- Show me in the TV book. - lt's not on TV yet.
那你就还不能上墙
Well, then it's not on the wall yet.
好吧  我拿录影带给你看
Okay, fine. l will bring you a tape.
你手边有麦特·劳尔的衣服吗
So, now, do you have any of Matt Lauer's clothes?
有可能吗  就是还没洗过的那种
Maybe? Just ones that haven't been cleaned yet?
天啊
God.
我爱博物馆
l love museums.
接受文化薰陶
Soaking up all the culture.
-要先去哪里  礼品贩卖部  -也对
- Where do you want to start? - The gift shop!
-然后去吃饭  -好  但我不能吃太多
- And then lunch. - Yes, but l can't eat too much.
保罗今晚要带我去吃饭
Paul's taking me out to dinner tonight.
他说会有个大惊喜
He said he has a big surprise planned.
他会不会要说他是同性恋
Do you think maybe he's gonna tell you he's gay?
什么  为什么
What? No, why?
不为什么  那样真的会很惊喜  对吗
No reason. That would just be a really big surprise, right?
红毯可以铺在这边
You could put the aisle over here
然后在这边证婚
and have the wedding ceremony over here.
原来这里可以结婚
l didn't know you could get married here.
这里当礼堂的确很美
This would be a beautiful place to get married.
但我不会把红毯铺在那边
But l wouldn't put the aisle there.
更不会在那边证婚
And l would never have the ceremony there.
应该在这个漂亮的拱门下证婚
You'd have the ceremony under a beautiful arch.
有什么事吗
May l help you?
抱歉打断你
Sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt.
这里很美
lt's just such a beautiful space.
-经常举办婚礼吗  -是的  我们很受欢迎
- Do you do a lot of weddings? - Yes, we're popular.
预约已经排到两年后了  抱歉
There's a two- year waiting list. Sorry.
莫妮卡  你也应该去预约
Monica, you should put your name down for this place.
什么  你疯了吗
What? Are you crazy?
我又不结婚  我甚至还没订婚
l'm not getting married. l'm not even engaged.
但反正要等两年
But there's a two- year wait.
要是你两年后订了婚了呢
What if you get engaged in two years?
还得再等两年呢
Then you've got to wait another two years for this place?
那就四年了  钱德勒才不会等那么久
That's four years. Chandler's not gonna wait that long.
他会去找别人
He's gonna find somebody else.
某个有预约的人
Someone who did put their name on the list.
先预约又不会有什么损失
lt can't hurt to put your name down.
要是两年后没订婚  就放弃不用嘛
lf, in two years, you're not engaged, you just don't use it.
先预约的确不会有什么损失
l guess there is no harm in putting my name down.
我也要预约
l'm gonna do it too.
我也要
Me too!
真的吗  你要嫁给谁
Really? Who would you marry?
我不知道  我现在还没有对象
I don’t know, I don’t have anyone right now. Y’know?
菲比
Oh, Pheebs.
别为我难过  至少我的男朋友不是同性恋
Don't feel too sorry for me. At least my boyfriend isn't gay.
菲比  这样不...
Phoebe, that's not...
别逼我开始说你家那个
Don't even get me started on yours.
-你看过我那部戏的录影带了吗  -看过了
- Did you watch the tape of my show? - l did.
好  让我回墙上吧
Alright. Let's get me back up there.
不行  你不能上墙
No. You don't go up on the wall.
为什么  可你看过我的戏了啊
What? But you saw the show.
对  它冒犯了我的同胞
Yes. It was very offensive to my people.
干洗店老板吗
Dry cleaners?
俄国人  片子里俄国人全是恐怖分子和恶棍
Russians. lt showed them as terrorists and villains.
好  你看  你有哈里逊·福特
Okay, okay. Look, you got Harrison Ford up there!
没错  福特先生是个好顾客
That's right. Mr. Ford is a very good customer.
他带很多衣服来  你却两手空空
He brings us a lot of clothes; you bring us nothing!
或许吧
Okay, that may be true.
但在《空军一号》里
But in Air Force One, okay,
俄国人是恐怖分子  很邪恶
the Russians were terrorists and evil!
他还杀了一堆俄国人  那样很冒犯你们
And plus, he kills a bunch of them. That's offensive to Russians.
-那片我没看过  -你应该看一下  超棒
- l've never seen it. - You should. lt's great!
这里真的好漂亮
This place is really beautiful.
对啊  我从小就经常来
Yeah. l've been coming here since l was a kid.
这里以前是我奶奶家
This used to be my grandma's.
我只有我奶奶的眼睛
The only thing l got from my grandmother was her eyes.
我不是说有她的眼珠子
l mean, not her actual eyeballs.
大家都说我的眼睛随她...
But people say that my eyes look....
要不要来亲热
Do you wanna make out?
好啊
Sure.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
怎么了
What's wrong?
我只是想到你爸爸
Yeah. l was just thinking about your father.
只要你能兴奋就好
Well, whatever works for you.
不是
No.
他之前有点把我吓到了
He just really freaked me out before.
我们不过是得再多瞒着一个人而已
So we have to hide our relationship from one more person.
那又怎样
Big deal.
况且我们一直很乐在其中
Besides, we've had fun hiding it.
也对
Yeah.
怎么了
Yeah?
你有准备防护措施吗
You brought protection, right?
怎么了  这里有熊吗
Why, are there, like, bears or something?
你是说那个啊  没有
Protection. Yeah. No, yeah.
那个我忘带了
That... That l forgot.
那我去买商店买吧
I’ll just run to the store and get some.
不  我是男人  我去买
Oh no. Hey. l'm the guy. l'll get it.
-你知道商店在哪里吗  -不知道
- Do you know where the store is? - No.
你想骑粉红脚踏车在街上到处转吗
Do you wanna ride around town on my little pink bicycle?
有点想
A little bit.
我十分钟后回来
l'll be back in 1 0 minutes.
好的
Okay.
你何不先进浴缸里等我
Why don't you get in the hot tub and l'll meet you there.
天啊  好棒的惊喜
Oh, my God! What a great surprise!
这栋房子好漂亮
This is such a beautiful house!
谢谢  这是我妈的房子  这里是厨房
Thank you. lt used to be my mother's. This is the kitchen.
这里是莫妮卡和钱德勒的家
You've reached Monica and Chandler's.
如果你听到这则留言  我们可能在筛选电话
lf you're listening to this message, we're probably screening.
就是
Yeah, we are.
我是摩根却斯博物馆的海蒂
Hi, this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.
我要找莫妮卡·盖勒
l'm calling for Monica Geller.
我想告诉她  有人取消预约
l wanted to let her know that there was a cancellation.
如果她还有兴趣
lf she's still interested in
在我们这里举办宾-盖勒联姻
having the Bing- Geller wedding in our facility...
请把握机会
...it is available...
我是钱德勒·宾  我是钱德勒·宾
This is Chandler Bing! This is Chandler Bing!
是的  我是新郎
Yes, the groom.
不  我不是
No, not the groom!
这里好幽静
lt's so secluded up here.
我知道  所以我喜欢这里
l know. That's why l like it here.
全世界好像只剩我们两个人
l feel like we're the only two people in the world.
抱歉
Sorry.
怎么了  亲爱的
What's the matter, honey?
你看到老鼠了吗
Did you see a little mouse?
不是  大熊  外面有大熊
No! Big bear! Big bear outside!
你要不要...
l think l....
要不要去看一下
Actually, would you go check on that?
亲爱的  这里没有熊
Honey. We don't have any bears here.
好吧
Well, okay.
帮我倒杯健怡可乐好吗
Would you get me a Diet Coke?
-好  我马上回来  -好
- Okay. Be right back. - Okay.
-你在这里干嘛  -你又在这里干嘛
- What are you doing here? - What are you doing here?
-我是跟保罗来的  -我认出他的脚踝了
- l came with Paul! - Yeah. l recognized the ankles.
快点  快出来
Hurry up. Get out.
拿去吧  宝贝
Here you go, honey.
-谢谢你  -健怡可乐
- Thank you! - Diet Coke.
冰块
lce.
我要冰块
l need ice.
好
Okay.
-谢谢你  -我马上回来
- Thank you. - Be right back.
好
Okay.
又是冰块这一招
You and your ice.
出来  快点  快走
Get out! Get out! Go! Come on!
不行  不行  他在那里面
No, not in there! Not in there! He's in there!
-你真的听到熊叫了吗  -进去啦
- Did you really hear a bear? - Go!
来了  宝贝
Here you go, honey.
一杯加冰的健怡可乐
One Diet Coke with ice.
谢谢
Thank you.
你能来  我真开心
l am so happy that you're here.
-我回来了  -伊丽莎白
- Here l am! - Elizabeth!
看  伊丽莎白来了
Look! Elizabeth's here!
你在跟谁说话
Who were you talking to?
你们啊
You guys?
你怎么知道我们在这里
How did you know we were here?
她一定是看到往车库的方向有轮胎痕
She obviously saw the tire tracks leading up to the closed garage.
是啊
Obviously.
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth,
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
你是来这里赶报告什么的吗
Did you come up here to work on that term paper or something?
没错
Yeah.
那你不如去那个房间写吧
Well, why don't you go in that room and do your homework?
我不会去那个房间写  那是我爸的卧房
l wouldn't do it in there. That's my dad's bedroom.
那是你爸的卧房
That's your dad's bedroom.
That's your dad's bedroom!
你干嘛这么大声
Why are you yelling?
这杯健怡可乐  让我好兴奋啊
That Diet Coke, l think, just straight to my head!
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
待会儿见
See you later.
慢着  我买了东西要帮你煮晚餐
Wait. l bought groceries. l was gonna make you dinner.
下次先过问我好吗
Well, next time, ask!
或等我先开口嘛
Or at least wait for me to ask!
我是摩根却斯博物馆的海蒂
Hi, this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.
-我要找莫妮卡盖勒  -完了
- l'm calling for Monica Geller. - Oh, no.
我想告诉她  有人取消预约
l wanted to let her know that there was a cancellation.
如果她还有兴趣
lf she's still interested
在我们这里举办宾-盖勒联姻
in having the Bing- Geller wedding in our facility...
请把握机会
...it is available....
拜托  他没听到  他没听到
Please. He didn't hear it!
我是钱德勒·宾  我是钱德勒·宾
This is Chandler Bing! This is Chandler Bing!
不
No!
有什么事吗
Can l help you?
那个能决定谁的照片能上墙的人呢
Yeah, where's the guy who decides whose pictures go up on the wall?
-他现在不在  -不会吧
- He's not here right now. - You're kidding me!
记得告诉他
Make sure you tell him
乔伊·崔比安尼带了一堆衣服来
that Joey Tribbiani stopped by to drop off all these clothes.
我是个演员  我想让我的照片上墙
l'm an actor. l'm trying to get my picture on the wall.
其实有两个人能决定这件事呢
You know, there are two people who could get your picture up there.
是吗
Oh, really?
也许我们应该去喝一杯
Well, maybe you and l go out for drinks.
你是另外一个人  对吧
You're the other one, right?
丽莎  你今晚要留下来吗
So, Lizzie, are you planning on staying the night?
不了  相信我  我会尽快离开
No, no. Believe me, l'm leaving as soon as possible.
那好...  不是我们不要你留下来
Good. Not that we don't want you to stay.
我们也很想你留下
Obviously, you're welcome.
你还有多少功课
How much more homework do you have?
只剩一个问题不知道怎么解决
l just have one problem left that l do not know how to solve.
瑞秋  也许你可以上楼来帮我
Rachel, maybe you wanna come upstairs and help me figure it out?
是吗
Really?
好
Okay.
好吧  我上楼
Okay, l'll go upstairs...
你去车上帮我拿东西
...if you get me something from the car.
你要拿什么东西
What do you need from the car?
给我惊喜啊
Surprise me.
好
Okay.
你要去车上  我要去楼上
So you're gonna be in the car! l will be upstairs!
这就是目前的状况
That's where everybody's gonna be!
放轻松  放轻松  你表现得很好
Just relax. Relax, Paul. You're doing great.
她喜欢你
She likes you.
她喜欢你  她喜欢你
l think she likes you. She likes you.
为什么   因为你是个"好男儿"
You know why? Because you're a neat guy.
你是男子汉
You are the man.
You are the man!
还是很有料
Still got it.
很性感
Still sexy.
你是个爱情机器
You're just a love machine.
我只是个爱情机器
I'm just the love machine.
该上场了
Showtime.
-菲比  怎么了
- Phoebe? - Yeah?
-你有见到钱德勒吗  -没有  怎么了
- Have you seen Chandler? - No, why?
博物馆那个女人打来说  有人取消预约
The museum called and said that there was a cancellation...
我们可以提前举行婚礼  结果钱德勒听见了
...and that we could move up our wedding. And Chandler heard.
就是啊  你觉得有多严重
l know. How bad is this?
对一般男人来说  很严重
Well, with a regular guy, it's bad.
但是对钱德勒...不敢想象
With Chandler, oh, dear God!
我知道  他被吓到了  我到处都找不到他
l know! And he totally freaked out. l can't find him anywhere!
你要怎么办
What are you gonna do?
反正我再也不听你的话了
l'm never going to listen to you again, that's for sure.
"先预约又不会有什么损失"
"What harm can it do if you put your name down?"
-那是瑞秋说的  -瑞秋不在这里嘛
- Rachel said that. - Well, Rachel's not here!
在这里
Here it is!
乔伊  你为什么要签"畜生"
Joey, why did you sign it "son of a bitch"?
-我没有啊  这是谁干的  -畜生
- l didn't do that. Who would do that? - Son of a bitch!
好吧  那问他好了
Okay. Maybe ask this guy.
-你  滚出我的店  -他做了什么
- You! Get out of my shop! - What did he do?
-他泡了我老婆  -乔伊
- He went out with my wife! - Joey!
我没有跟你老婆约会  好吗
l did not go out with your wife! Okay?
我是跟她约会
l went out with her.
她就是我老婆
That's my wife!
滚出去
Get out!
-我们还是走好了  -对啊
- Well, we should go. - Yeah.
罗斯
Ross?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth!
好  我从窗户爬出去
Okay. l'm gonna go out this window.
我们前门见
l'll meet you at the front door.
你就跟他们说你要回家  好吗
Just tell them you're going home. OK?
-好  -等等  别进去
- Okay. - Wait! No, don't go in there!
别进去  我还要喝汽水呢
Don't go in there! l need another soda!
罗斯
Ross!
天啊  罗斯  你在这里干什么
Oh, my God, Ross! What in heaven's name are you doing here?
所以我们不能再见面了
And that is why we cannot see each other anymore.
罗斯  我们得好好谈一谈
Ross, you and l are gonna have to have a little talk.
-爸  -接着就是你
- Daddy, l... - You're next!
好  我不知道他有来
Okay. l didn't know he was here.
让我把话问清楚
Let me just see if l got this straight.
我叫你离我女儿远一点  否则就让你被开除
l tell you to stay away from my daughter or l'll have you fired.
结果你听到的是  "带我女儿"
What you heard was: "Take my daughter...
"到我乡下的别墅"
...come up to my country house
"破坏我和瑞秋的周末"
and ruin my weekend with Rachel. "
拜托  保罗  听我解释
Please, Paul. Just let me explain.
不  你听我说  开除
No! Let me explain! Fired!
好  开除就开除
Okay, fine. Fine. Have me fired.
我只想你知道
But l want you to know...
我们也没那么不同
that you and l are not all that different. l mean
我也是"好男儿"
...l, too, am a "neat guy. "
什么
What?
我也是
And l, too...
个爱情机器
am "just a love machine. "
罗斯
Ross.
-我带你去客房  -没问题
- Let me show you where the guest room is. - Okay.
对不起  你别再害怕了
l'm so sorry. Please stop freaking out.
我没有害怕啊
l'm not freaking out.
我干嘛害怕   有个叫海蒂的女人打来
Why would l? A woman named Hildy called
说我们要结婚了
and said we were getting married.
但这是常有的事
But that happens every day.
亲爱的  那个地方很漂亮
Honey, we were at this beautiful place...
我是因为好玩  才预约的
...and l just put our names down for fun.
-又不会有什么损失  -损失在这里
- l mean, what's the harm in that? - Right here.
钱德勒  你千万别以为我想逼婚
Chandler. Please don't think l was trying to pressure you.
-菲比和瑞秋觉得  -菲比和瑞秋
- Phoebe and Rachel thought... - Phoebe and Rachel?
所以比我早知道我们要结婚的  有你
So the people that knew about our wedding before me were you...
菲比和瑞秋  海蒂
...Phoebe and Rachel, Hildy,
和一个叫星光魔力的乐团
and some band called the Starlight Magic Seven...
对了  他们也有空
...who are available, by the way.
我错了
lt was a mistake.
拜托不要误会  我完全没有那个意思
Please don't take this to mean anything, because it doesn't.
好吧
Okay.
真的吗
Really?
如果你真的没有那个意思
Yes. lf it really doesn't mean anything,
你知道我还没准备好
because you know l'm just not ready.
我知道
l know.
好
Okay.
好吧
All right.
我去告诉乔伊你回来了
l'm gonna go tell Joey that you're back.
我们刚才好担心
We were really worried about you.
她相信了吗
Did she buy it?
相信了
Totally.
-海蒂有带你参观吗   -有  那里好漂亮
- So did Hildy show you the place? - Yeah. lt's beautiful.
真不敢相信  你居然要跟莫妮卡求婚了
l can't believe you're gonna ask Monica to marry you.
就是啊
l know.
-甘瑟  -把这些卡布奇诺端到11桌
- Hey, Gunther. - Take these cappuccinos to table 1 1 .
那个男的要意大利脆棒
And that guy wants some biscotti.
我只是要外带一杯咖啡
l just actually came in for a cup of coffee to go.
你还在这里打工吗
Do you still work here?
没有  我早就不做了
No. l quit a long time ago.
我没有告诉你吗   抱歉
Did l forget to tell you that? l'm sorry.
-没事  反正我也打算开除你  -太好了
- That's cool. l was gonna fire you anyway. - Great!